<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Stuart John Wayland</title>
    <link>https://stuartwayland.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Stuart John Wayland</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language><atom:link href="https://stuartwayland.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://stuartwayland.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stuartwayland.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>About  Link to heading   Hi everyone! My name is Stuart (I also go by Stu) and I&amp;rsquo;m a 3rd year computer science PhD student at the University of California, Santa Cruz (Baskin School of Engineering). At the moment, I&amp;rsquo;m interested in exploring the intersectionality of mathematics and computer science, and hope to continue to study mathematics capable of bringing new perspective to familiar computer science problems. Check out my Research to see what I&amp;rsquo;ve been up to!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://stuartwayland.github.io/cv/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stuartwayland.github.io/cv/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://stuartwayland.github.io/extracurriculars/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stuartwayland.github.io/extracurriculars/</guid>
      <description>First Response  Link to heading   One of my interests outside of academia is learning about first response. It has always been a goal of mine to work as ski patrol and participate in moutain search and rescue. I&amp;rsquo;ve spent a considerable amount of time in the mountains, during which I&amp;rsquo;ve leared how quickly things can go wrong! Learning about first response started as a necessary preparatory measure to continue to engage in extreme outdoor sports, but it has turned into a significant point of interest in my life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://stuartwayland.github.io/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stuartwayland.github.io/research/</guid>
      <description>Research  Link to heading   Quantum: Algorithms and Information  Link to heading   I have the pleasure of working with Professor Alexandra Kolla&amp;rsquo;s Quantum Algorithms research group here in Santa Cruz. We&amp;rsquo;ve spent the last year or so working on approximation algorithms for different Mathematical spin glass systems. Check out our papers, &amp;ldquo;Approximation Algorithms for Quantum Max-d-Cut&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Monogamy of Entanglement Bounds and Improved Approximation Algorithms for Qudit Hamiltonians&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://stuartwayland.github.io/transcripts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stuartwayland.github.io/transcripts/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
